Finding Aid for the USA for Africa Records LSC.1669
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Development Education
  - Development Education (Box 124, Folder 9-11, 13-14, 16)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Unfoldered Material. (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Summary. (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - General. (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Guidelines. (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - U.S.A. for Africa. (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - Hands Across America. (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - Unfoldered Material. (Box 124, Folder 17)
  - Harvard Institute (Box 124, Folder 18-20)
    - World Development Education - Correspondence - DE802. (Box 124, Folder 18)
    - Project Summary - DE802. (Box 124, Folder 19)
    - Financial information - DE802. (Box 124, Folder 20)
  - YMCA (Box 124, Folder 21-24)
    - Project Summary - DE804. (Box 124, Folder 21)
    - Progress Report - DE804. (Box 124, Folder 22)
    - Financial information - DE804. (Box 124, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence - DE804. (Box 124, Folder 24)
  - Development Institute UCLA (Box 125, Folder 1-2, 4)
    - Correspondence - DE807. (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Project Summary - DE807. (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Financial information - DE807. (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - UCLA - Progress Report - DE807. (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Overseas Education Fund (OEF) (Box 125, Folder 5-8)
    - Progress Report - DE815. (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Project Summary - DE815. (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Financial information - DE815. (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - DE815. (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Roosevelt Center (Box 125, Folder 9-12)
    - Project Summary - DE817. (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - DE817. (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - Financial information - DE817. (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Progress Report - DE817. (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - Children's Express (Box 125, Folder 13-17)
    - Correspondence - DE818. (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Financial information - DE818. (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - Progress Report - DE818. (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - Project Summary - DE818. (Box 125, Folder 16)
    - [No further description available]. (Box 125, Folder 17)
  - Africare (Box 125, Folder 18-21)
    - Progress Report - DE819. (Box 125, Folder 18)
    - Project Summary - DE819. (Box 125, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - DE819. (Box 125, Folder 20)
    - Financial information - DE819. (Box 125, Folder 21)
  - Washington Office on Africa (Box 126, Folder 1-5)
    - Progress Report - DE820. (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - DE820. (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Project Summary - DE820. (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Financial information - DE820. (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Unfoldered Material. (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - TransAfrica Forum (Box 126, Folder 6-9)
    - Project Summary - DE821. (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Progress Report - DE821. (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - DE821. (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Financial information - DE821. (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - I.D.C. (Box 126, Folder 10-13)
    - Correspondence - DE826. (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Financial information - DE826. (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - Project Summary - DE826. (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - Progress Report - DE826. (Box 126, Folder 13)
- Development Education - Rejects
  - New York University - Jack Robertson - Africa - "The Quiet Revolution" (film) - no.803. (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - International Institute for Environment and Development - "From the ground up in Africa" - no.805. (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Global Tomorrow Coalition - no.810. (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Lutheran World Relief - no.813. (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - South-North News Service - no.816. (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - League of Women Voters - no.822. (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - World Neighbors - no.823. (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Citizen's Network / Foreign Affairs - no.827. (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Global perspectives in education - no.828. (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - National Council of Churches - no.829. (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - National Committee for World Food Day - no.832. (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Maryknoll Fathers - no.834. (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Oxfam/U.S. - no.835. (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - National Council of R.P.C.V.'s - no.840. (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 127, Folder 15)
  - African American Labor Center - no.845. (Box 127, Folder 16)
  - C.O.D.E.L. (Box 127, Folder 17)
  - Oxfam/U.S. - no.847. (Box 127, Folder 18)
  - Hunger & Development Coalition of Central Ohio - no.848. (Box 127, Folder 19)
  - World Education, Incorporated: "Connecting the world with the campus" - no.849. (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - World view - no.850. (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - World Hunger Year - no.853. (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - A.S.T.C. - Association of Science - Tech Centers - "World Food Day" - Museum exhibit - no.855. (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Photo exhibit - David Heiden - no.857. (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Lasting Links - no.858. (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - U.U.S.C. / Africa Peace Committee - no.859. (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - The Geopeace Institute - global co-exixtence conference - no.801. (Box 128, Folder 9)
- Development Resources
  - "Hands Across America" [video tape]. (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Repertoire des Organisations non Governementales du secteur sylvicole. (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Old Doctrines vs. New Threats. (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - U.S.A. for Africa - Three year report. (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - U.S.A. for Africa - report., 1988 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - "We Are The World." (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Hands Across America - Official record book. (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - United Nations Office of Emergency Operations in Africa. (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - United Nations Food & Agriculture Organization. (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Roosevelt Center for American Policy Studies. (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - National Council of Negro Women, Incorporated. (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - U.S.A. for Africa - Recovery and development programs. (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Synergos Institute. (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - World Conservation Union - Sahel program - reports. (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Eastern & Southern African Management Institute. (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - S.A.F.T.E. (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - African Peace Tour., 1987 & 1988 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Populations United Nations point de vue africain. (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - C.W.L.A. (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Rapport d'activites annual - Niger., 1988 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Etude pour le C.C.A. - Non-governmental organization - Mali. (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - U.S.A. for Africa field monitoring report. (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - "In Whose Interest?" (book by Kevin Danaher). (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - "Arms and Hunger" (book by Willy Brandt). (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Directory for Non-governmental organizations in the forestry sector. (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - International Symposium - Bamako., 1985 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous publications. (Box 121, Folder 3)
- Ethiopia & Others - Rejections
  - Ethipoia - Rejected proposals (Box 160, Folder 1-3)
    - "Proposals not recommended for funding" to "Tigray" no.401. (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - "Surgical aid to children" to "Proj Ethiopia." (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - [No further description available]. (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Mozambique. (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Niger. (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Senegal. (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - Mali. (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Chad. (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - Burkina Faso. (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Mauritania. (Box 162, Folder 2)
- General Resources
  - "United Nations Office for Emergency Operations in Africa." (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Publications/pamphlets re Africa. (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Program Review Board. (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Foreign language (Ethiopian) publications. (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Islamic African Relief Agency. (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - "Africa: A background kit for non-governmental organizations." (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Funding proposals to the Program Review Board. (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - "Sarh community development program." (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - World bank. (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Development-related publications. (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous publications. (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous proposals. (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - "Liste des documents a envoyer a Monsieur Jalal." (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Ethiopian Red Cross. (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - "Operations-level management development." (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Index to U.S.A. for Africa projects. (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Reports & conferences re women. (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Annual reports & lectures. (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - "Africa Peace Tour." (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - SataLife proposal to USA/FA. (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Foreign language & bilingual magazines. (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous English language Africa-related magazines. (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous reports. (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Activity reports. (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - C.A.R.E. - Sudan. (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Women. (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - "Research papers on women - food security by A.A.W.O.R.D.." (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous books. (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Literacy & education. (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Mozambique. (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous publications. (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous organizations. (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - "Debt conversion workshop." (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Annual reports. (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - AICF. (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Development education. (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Panos Institute. (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Ethiopian Red Cross. (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Donor publications. (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - C.R.D.A. (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Ethiopia. (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Oxfam/U.S. (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - South Africa. (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Foreign language publications. (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - African Development Bank. (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Sudan. (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Reports on women. (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - United Nations publications. (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Togo. (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Dakar (Senegal) conference. (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Burkina Faso. (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Chad. (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Carter Center. (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Angola. (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - "InterAction Forum." (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Kenya. (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - World College West. (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - R.E.S.A.D.O.L. (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Globescope. (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Ivory Coast. (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous publications. (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Ethiopia. (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - "UN development fund for women." (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Literacy & education. (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Development Group for Alternative Policies. (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Development-related. (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Children. (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - "The Network." (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - "UN emergency situation in Mozambique." (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - "I.R.E.D. Forum." (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Annual reports. (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Chad. (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Mozambique. (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - U.S. and Africa related. (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Trickle Up program. (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Hands Across America. (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - InterAction. (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - United Nations publications. (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Comic Relief. (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Oxfam/U.S. (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Caribbean-oriented relief. (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - "I.U.C.N. Sahel programme." (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Internation Monetary Fund. (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Women's International Network. (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - "Background Notes." (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - "Global Pages." (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous organizations. (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Non-governmental development organizations. (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - AF press clips. (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - S.A.D.C.C. - Non-governmental organizations. (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Popular magazines. (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Rapport de session - l'Institut Africain pour le Devloppement Economique et Social Formation. (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Third World Information Network, Limited. (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - U.S.A. for Africa domestic grants. (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - United Nations Office for Emergency Operations in Africa. (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Annual reports. (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - UNICEF. (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Angola. (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - "Background Notes." (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Mozambique. (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - "Ecoafrica." (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Development. (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Newsletters. (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Breakthrough on Hunger. (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising. (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Foreign Policy. (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Reports on women. (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - F.D.E.A. (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - R.P.P.F. (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Mauritania. (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - A.A.W.O.R.D. (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - World College West. (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - African Peace Committee. (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - C.I.F.A.D. (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - O.M.A. (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Islamic African Relief Agency. (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous pamphlets. (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - United Nations Status Report on the Emergency Situation in Africa. (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - United Nations Emergency Situation in Angola. (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - United Nations Emergency Situation in Mozambique. (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Women and the Law in Botswana. (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Hunger projects. (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Mozambique. (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - World health. (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Hands Across America. (Box 115, Folder 8)
- Medical Task Force - Rejects & Resource Material
  - Ethiopia and Sudan - Newsclippings. (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - West Africa - Newsclippings. (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - Opportunities Industrialization Centers International - Unfoldered Material. (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Eco-Africa - Unfoldered Material. (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - Caritas - Mauritania - 05202 "Emer. Med. Supplies for Nat'l Tuberculosis Prog." (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - Unsolicited Proposals - International Heart Relief - Minnesota. (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - Africa Peace Committee - Peace Tour - General information - U.U.S.C. (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - Guidelines on Immunizations - Sudan - Resource. (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - General information on Somalia. (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - Newsclippings. (Box 163, Folder 10)
  - Helen Keller International - General information on Mauritania. (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - Food and Nutrition Monitoring Project - Kenya. (Box 163, Folder 12)
  - American College of Nurses - Midwives. (Box 163, Folder 13)
  - M.S.F. - Belgium Yaws - Mali. (Box 163, Folder 14)
  - International Child Resource Institute - Berkeley - Swaziland. (Box 163, Folder 15)
  - Cunique Samaritain - Ivory Coast. (Box 163, Folder 16)
  - International Child Health and Diarrhoeal Disease Foundation - Ref. (Box 163, Folder 17)
  - New York Medical College. (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Ministry of Health - Mozambique. (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - University of North Carolina - M.T.F. - Reject - Kenya. (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - University of Rochester - Rejects. (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - World Vision. (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - Managing Sciences for Health - Managing Drug Supply. (Box 164, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Rejections, 1987-1990
  - Undes. proposals - Rejection letters. (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Helen Keller International. (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Association Burkinabe d'Action Communautaire. (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Love the Children - Ethiopia - FP07. (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Unity Family Service Organization. (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Integrated Holistic Approach. (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Planned Parenthood Federation - International division. (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Association Malienne pour le Development et la Cooperation. (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Association Malienne pour la Promotion du Sahel. (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - C.A.R.E. - Mali. (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Globe Contact. (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Kilabo / Mali. (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Corps de Bienfaisance. (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - Technap. (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - I.R.E.D. (Box 129, Folder 15)
  - Union des Geoupements Paysans de Diogo - Senegal. (Box 129, Folder 16)
  - Eglise Evangelique Lutherienne du Senegal. (Box 129, Folder 17)
  - A.R.E.A.S. - Senegal. (Box 129, Folder 18)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 129, Folder 19)
  - Community Aid Abroad. (Box 129, Folder 20)
  - American Refugee Committee. (Box 129, Folder 21)
  - G.O.A.L. (Box 129, Folder 22)
  - Development education - Africa Peace Committee. (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - N.C.I.H. - "International Health Scholars End." (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - State University at Cortland - Eritrean film. (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Africa Fund - South Africa Now. (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - R.P.C.V. - development Ed. (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - International Institute for Environment Development - FP11. (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - ToyoMedia. (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - I.D.E.X. / San Francisco. (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Church World Service. (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Salem Merkuria - "Reaching for the Will." (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - University of Texas - Health Science Center. (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Carter Center. (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - Essential information - "Gift of Life Project" - FP01. (Box 130, Folder 13)
  - Rejected / Indiana University. (Box 130, Folder 14)
  - InterAction. (Box 130, Folder 15)
  - Panos - Seminar in Sudan - FP02. (Box 130, Folder 16)
  - AmFAR. (Box 130, Folder 17)
  - U.N.P.A.A.E.R.D. - United Nations Program of Action for African R&D. (Box 130, Folder 18)
  - Iceberg Project. (Box 130, Folder 19)
  - Action Aid. (Box 130, Folder 20)
  - Children's Fund for Southern Africa. (Box 130, Folder 21)
  - Talent Consortium. (Box 130, Folder 22)
  - Development through self-reliance - "Feature film on women's rights" - FP04. (Box 130, Folder 23)
  - Live by Faith Mission - Zambia - FP06. (Box 130, Folder 24)
  - Mogbeleh Agricultural Project - Sierra Leon - FP05. (Box 130, Folder 25)
  - Federacion Apoyo Familiar - Argentina - rejection letter. (Box 130, Folder 26)
  - University of Botswana. (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Geopeace Institute. (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Namibian returnees self-help project. (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Uganda Women Tree Planting Movement. (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - C.E.A.P.A. (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - African Enterprise. (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Zaire. (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Ngargboma Agricultural Development Project. (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Culture in Another South Africa. (Box 131, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous Resource Material
  - Awards from the Government of Sudan. (Box 116, Folder 1-7)
  - U.S.A. for Africa reports. (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Relief and rehabilitation commission. (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Youth Ending Hunger Launch. (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Sudan. (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - UNICEF. (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Ethiopia. (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - A.A.L.A.E. (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - "We Are The World." (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - U.S. & Third World. (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Panos Institute. (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Africa Exchange. (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - United Nations Office of Emergency Operations in Africa. (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Report - unidentified author. (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Carter Center. (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Manuscript for journal article. (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - U.S.A. for Africa proposal. (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Malnutrition in Moshi District. (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Kenya. (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Annual reports. (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous publications. (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - H.S.D. (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - United Nations publications. (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - "Monday Developments." (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - "African News." (Box 187, Folder 2)
  - "West Africa." (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - "Africa Report." (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - "World Hunger Year." (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - "Africa Demos." (Box 187, Folder 6)
  - "C.R.D.A. News." (Box 187, Folder 7)
  - Evaluation related. (Box 187, Folder 8)
  - World College West. (Box 187, Folder 9)
  - Center for International Development & Education. (Box 187, Folder 10)
  - "Africa Review.", 1985 (Box 187, Folder 11)
  - World hunger related. (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - "World Hunger." (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - U.S. & Third World related. (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - Global Health Council (NCIH). (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - Ethiopia. (Box 188, Folder 5)
  - Unitarian Universalist Service Committee. (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - "Child Resource World Review." (Box 188, Folder 7)
  - "Action" - National Volunteer Agency. (Box 188, Folder 8)
  - Faidika. (Box 188, Folder 9)
  - "Brundtland Bulletin." (Box 188, Folder 10)
  - Hands Across America - Giant Hands Arch [drawing]. (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - "Worldwatch Paper." (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - Organization of African Unity. (Box 190, Folder 2)
  - Mozambique. (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - U.S.A. for Africa release / photo on African Development Fund., May 29, 1986 (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - U.S.A. for Africa news items - Africa related., 1985 (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - Newsclippings, etc. - re U.S.A. for Africa trip to Africa. (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Newsclippings, etc. - re fund raisers. (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - U.S.A. for Africa newsclipings - "We Are The World.", 1985 (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - U.S.A. for Africa newsclipings - "We Are The World.", 1986 (Box 192, Folder 6)
  - Unlabelled folder. (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Africa newsclippings., 1987 (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - I.C.V.A. members. (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - Poets for Africa. (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Dave Fulton's article in "The World & I." (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - Spin article on Live Aid. (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - Rejected concept papers - Senegal. (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - Rejected concept papers - Sudan. (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous publications. (Box 193, Folder 8)
  - "Africa Leadership Forum." (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - "News from Africa Watch." (Box 193, Folder 10)
  - Handicap International - Mozambique [VHS]., 1989 (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous publications. (Box 197)
  - Africa news. (Box 209, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous publications from various organizations. (Box 219, Folder 1)
- Photos / Photo Albums
  - U.S.A. for Africa funded G.P.A.R. - Semada project - Ethiopia. (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - "We Are The World" scrapbook. (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - Photo album - United nations Development Fund - Small irrigation projects in the Gao and Timbuctu regions of Mali. (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Photo album - Medical Benevolence Foundation - Construction of CME facility (Zaire). (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified album. (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Photo album - J.A.C.R.D.A. complex - Addis Adaba - Ethiopia. (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Photo album - untitled - Sudan., (2 albums) (Box 169, Folder 2-3)
  - Loose photo album leaves - CPAR - Spring capping construction., June 1988 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - Loose photos. (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - "Photos of African Projects." (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Bitter Harvest. (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Computer Library. (Box 170, Folder 4)
- Proposals / Communications / Information on Organizations, 1986-1988
  - Academy for Educational Development. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Action on Disability & Development. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Adventist Development and Relief Agency (ADRA) (Box 30, Folder 3-4)
    - Sudan. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Sudan proposals Ref. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Agence Europenne pour le Dveloppement et la Sant (AEDES) (Box 30, Folder 5-7)
    - Famine Early Warning System. (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Early Warning System. (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Proposal. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Africa "2000." (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - African American Institute. (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - African Medical Mission. (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Africare Niger. (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Africa - Press. (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - AIDS Project Los Angeles. (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - American Association for International Aging. (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - American Association for International Aging - Ref. (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - American College of Nurse-Midwives. (Box 30, Folder 16)